(Raj:)And not just because
(Raj:)you work around sea animals.
(Raj:)That actually
sounds interesting,
(Raj:)and I'd like
to learn more about it.
(Raj:)Hey, you okay?
(Howard:)Not really.
(Howard:)This guy shows up
out of the blue,
(Howard:)and now I have a brother?
(Howard:)My father has another family?
(Raj:)I get it.
(Raj:)What do you want to do?
(Howard:)I don't know. I...
(Howard:)I'd just like him to go away.
(Howard:)I can't deal with this.
(Raj:)All right, I've got your back.
(Howard:)Thank you. Come on.
(Howard:)And I'd like to point out
(Howard:)this wall just provided
a lot of privacy!
(Josh:)I can't believe
my brother's an astronaut.
(Josh:)That's amazing.
What was it like?
Listen, dude,
(Raj:)it's time for you
to hit the road.
(Howard:)Hey, hey, the young man asked
a good question.
(Wil:)So, for those of you
just tuning in,
(Wil:)we are listening
(Wil:)to a really fun fight
between my costar...
No, no, no.